ecoustics.com 2011-12-08

# eCoustics.com - Privacy Policy

Home > Privacy Policy (Last Updated: September 11, 2010) 

eCoustics, LLC ("eCoustics"), which owns and operates the website(s) under the domain name ("ecoustics.com") understand and respect the need for the privacy of its users. To keep you informed of our privacy policies, we have provided this document disclosing eCoustics' intent, purpose and use of possibly private information, and detailing the methods of gathering of such information. 

Visitors to eCoustics are not subject to involuntary information disclosure of any kind, other than those intrinsic to the operation of the site and the World Wide Web in general. Certain operations and features on eCoustics may require the use of cookies and/or the propagation of session information. These cookies and sessions facilitate the visitor's experience at eCoustics, but do not represent any other security or privacy concern outside of isolated, per visit session identification and/or recurring sessions for the purpose of storing and maintaining user submitted site preferences. 

eCoustics does not collect private information from its users without their knowledge. Generally, users who come to eCoustics are not required to disclose personal or private information. However, some special services such as forums and member content may require registration in order to allow full access to features. Further, eCoustics encourages users to provide cursory private and/or personal information to build the community aspect of the site, and to obtain basic group demographics data for statistical analysis. eCoustics does NOT sell, lease or rent to third parties, any private information linkable to a particular user and gathered through the registration process, without express consent from its users as indicated through information forms that users voluntarily fill out. 

From time to time, eCoustics may offer incentives to users in the form of contests, prizes, and giveaways, and request that users fill out surveys or questionnaires to qualify for participation in these special promotions. Unless explicitly indicated, information from these surveys, and questionnaires are used in group demographics studies and for better audience targeting - surveys and questionnaires related to contests **may** be subject to third party marketing companies. If you do not want your information subject to third party companies, do **not** fill out the contest surveys.

eCoustics will take reasonable precautionary measures to protect and safeguard all information gathered from its users for membership purposes. eCoustics does not, however, take any responsibility for any breach of security, accidental disclosure, theft, or tampering of its users' information.

#### Third Party Advertising

eCoustics uses third-party advertising companies and advertising networks to serve ads and collect information when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this Website, other sites and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. 

Personally identifiable information such as your name, address, email address or telephone number are not shared with advertisers without your permission. We may use personally identifiable information in order to fill in forms on third-party sites we use to present advertising offers. But this information will not be shared and will not be stored by any third parties if you decline these offers. Among the third-party advertising companies that eCoustics uses are Tremor Media, IDG TechNetwork, Google AdSense, Vibrant Media, Tribal Fusion. For more information on their privacy policies, please consult their respective Privacy Policies. 

#### Third Party Cookies

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. 

#### Privacy for Children - As per COPA

Although eCoustics generally targets to an adult audience, we welcome the visitation and participation of young users, with their parents' consent. It is strongly recommended that users under the age of 13 refrain from disclosing any personal and/or private information either through the user registration system, or through participation in questionnaires and surveys, and instead opt to remain anonymous in their participation of site activities. 

Please note that as of April 21st, 2000, the Child Online Protection Act of 1998 prohibits eCoustics from the collection of private information from users under the age of 13 without parental consent. Users under the age of 13 must provide a signed letter from their parents to indicate that they are aware of their child's activities on eCoustics and consent to these activities. This letter must be mailed or faxed to eCoustics Corporation, using the contact information below, before they can participate in activities requesting the disclosure of private information. 

Parents of our younger users may at any time, revoke their consent, and may request to review and edit the private information disclosed by sending a written request to eCoustics LCC via fax or mail. 

Though eCoustics will take reasonable measures to ensure that users under the age of 13 do not disclose their private information without first obtaining parental consent, the site cannot guarantee the protection of young users who choose not to disclose their age and who do not follow the requirements set forth by COPA. 

#### Privacy Contact Info:

**eCoustics, LLC**  
P.O Box 631  
San Francisco, CA 94104  
USA

Fax: (978) 285-5563
